[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Брати з собою' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "もっていきます"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Приносити з собою' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "もってきます"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Хвилюватись' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しんぱいします"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'хвилювання' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しんぱい"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відповідати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "こたえます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'відповідь' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "こたえ"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Нудота' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はきけ"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'відчувати нудоту' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はきけがします"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Кашель' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "せき"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'кашляти' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "せきがでます"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Живіт' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おなか"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Зуб' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "は"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the word 'Жар, гарячка' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ねつ"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the word 'Опік' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "やけど"
    }
]